<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DeFiChain</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/</link><description>Recent content on DeFiChain</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.defichain.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$DFI</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/dfi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/dfi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Bounty</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/bounty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/bounty/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DeFiChain app how-to</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/defi-app-how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/defi-app-how-to/</guid><description>Download the app Download the latest app from the downloads page.
Minimum requirements Requirement Minimum Required Memory 4GB OS macOS 10.14, Windows 10, Ubuntu LTS 18 and above Installing on macOS Step 1: Installation Open the downloaded image DeFi-Wallet-.dmg. In the Finder window that pops up, drag the DeFi Wallet on the left, on to the Applications directory shortcut on the right.</description></item><item><title>Developers</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/developers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/developers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DEX</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/dex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/dex/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DFI-BTC Airdrop</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/airdrop-6qfku6m2hp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/airdrop-6qfku6m2hp/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Downloads</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/downloads/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/foundation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/foundation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Learn</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Liquidity mining with DeFi app</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/liquidity-mining-how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/liquidity-mining-how-to/</guid><description>What is liquidity mining? Liquidity mining is a DeFi (decentralized finance) mechanism in which participants supply cryptocurrencies into liquidity pools, and being rewarded with fees and tokens based on their share of the total pool liquidity. Liquidity pools in DeFiChain consist of liquidity in pairs of coins, used by the DeFiChain DEX (Decentralized Exchange).
Adding liquidity Step 1: Launch the DeFiChain app Don't have the app installed yet? Click here for a step-by-step guide on how to do so.</description></item><item><title>Media</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/media/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/media/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Obtaining wrapped tokens</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/obtaining-wrapped-tokens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/obtaining-wrapped-tokens/</guid><description>To supply liquidity to the DEX and to liquidity mine, you will need not just DFI but tokens for the other side of the pool pair you wish to supply liquidity to. DeFiChain currently only support wrapped tokens, namely wrapped ETH, BTC and USDT.
If you also need DFI, you can watch our guide on where and how to buy DFI.
Method 1: Using the DEX The first method is right within the DeFi app.</description></item><item><title>Partners</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/partners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/partners/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>DEFICHAIN FOUNDATION LIMITED takes the privacy of your information seriously. This Privacy Policy applies to the defichain.com website (the “Website”) and governs data collection, processing and usage in compliance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (No. 26 of 2012) of Singapore (“PDPA”).
By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online.</description></item><item><title>Run a masternode</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/run-a-masternode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/run-a-masternode/</guid><description>Introduction Setting up a masternode on DefiChain allows you to participate in the consensus protocol and receive staking awards. One thing to note is that in order to set up a masternode, you must have a minimum of 20,000 DFI.
NOTE: This how-to expects some basic familiarity with the Linux terminal
Masternode roles There are two distinct roles: &amp;lsquo;masternode owner&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;masternode operator&amp;rsquo;. The owner holds the collateral and the primary activity (minting new coins, voting for anchors) is performed by operator.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/security/</guid><description>Audit 2: KnownSec Result PASS Number DeFiChain-GLSJ-20201020 Date October 20, 2020 Auditor Audit report Download Audit 1: Slow Mist Result PASS Number BCA002009180001 Date September 18, 2020 Auditor Audit report Download</description></item><item><title>Swap and arbitrage</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/swap-and-arbitrage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/swap-and-arbitrage/</guid><description>Swap using the DEX Swapping tokens on the DeFiChain DEX (Decentralized Exchange) is easy. At the time of writing, the DEX offers swap for the following pairs:
Ethereum–DeFiChain (ETH–DFI) Bitcoin–DeFiChain (BTC–DFI) Tether–DeFiChain (USDT–DFI) The DeFiChain DEX does not suffer the high gas fees of Ethereum-based DEX, due to network congestion. Afterall, Ethereum being a general purpose blockchain, isn't specifically designed for decentralized finance. DeFiChain on the other hand, is born and made for DeFi, and DeFi only.</description></item><item><title>Wallet encryption</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/wallet-encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/wallet-encryption/</guid><description>Notice: Encrypting your wallet via the console will cause your mnemonic phrase to change, do not rely on your mnemonic phrase as a backup if you follow this guide, instead make a backup after enabling encryption using backup files and store them in a secure location.
At the time of this writing, v2.1.4, the app does not yet have a graphical UI built-in to facilitate wallet encryption or locking. This can be a serious risk as your wallets can be compromised by any person or system having access to your wallet.</description></item><item><title>White paper</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/white-paper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/white-paper/</guid><description>Abstract: The DeFiChain Foundation is developing DeFiChain, a blockchain specifically dedicated to decentralized financial applications. By focusing on the functionality of the blockchain and dedicating it specifically to decentralized finance, DeFiChain provides unparalleled high transaction throughput, reduced risk of errors, and intelligent feature development specifically for the fulfillment of financial services on the blockchain.
This Document is not a Prospectus
This document does not constitute nor imply a prospectus of any sort.</description></item></channel></rss>