<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learns on DeFiChain</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/</link><description>Recent content in Learns on DeFiChain</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>All Rights Reserved</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.defichain.com/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DeFiChain app how-to</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/defi-app-how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/defi-app-how-to/</guid><description>Download the app Download the latest app from the downloads page.
Minimum requirements Requirement Minimum Required Memory 2GB OS macOS 10.14, Windows 10, Ubuntu LTS 18 and above Installing on macOS Step 1: Installation Open the downloaded image defi-app-.dmg. In the Finder window that pops up, drag the defi-app on the left, on to the Applications directory shortcut on the right.</description></item><item><title>Liquidity mining with DeFi app</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/liquidity-mining-how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/liquidity-mining-how-to/</guid><description>What is liquidity mining? Liquidity mining is a DeFi (decentralized finance) mechanism in which participants supply cryptocurrencies into liquidity pools, and being rewarded with fees and tokens based on their share of the total pool liquidity. Liquidity pools in DeFiChain consist of liquidity in pairs of coins, used by the DeFiChain DEX (Decentralized Exchange).
Adding liquidity Step 1: Launch the DeFiChain app Don't have the app installed yet? Click here for a step-by-step guide on how to do so.</description></item><item><title>Obtaining wrapped tokens</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/obtaining-wrapped-tokens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/obtaining-wrapped-tokens/</guid><description>To supply liquidity to the DEX and to liquidity mine, you will need not just DFI but tokens for the other side of the pool pair you wish to supply liquidity to. DeFiChain currently only support wrapped tokens, namely wrapped ETH, BTC and USDT.
If you also need DFI, you can watch our guide on where and how to buy DFI.
Method 1: Using the DEX The first method is right within the DeFi app.</description></item><item><title>Run a masternode</title><link>https://www.defichain.com/learn/run-a-masternode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.defichain.com/learn/run-a-masternode/</guid><description>Introduction Setting up a masternode on DefiChain allows you to participate in the consensus protocol and receive staking awards. One thing to note is that in order to set up a masternode, you must have a minimum of 1 million DFI tokens.
NOTE: This how-to expects some basic familiarity with the Linux terminal
Masternode roles There are two distinct roles: &amp;lsquo;masternode owner&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;masternode operator&amp;rsquo;. The owner holds the collateral and the primary activity (minting new coins, voting for anchors) is performed by operator.</description></item></channel></rss>